mmoabc.com 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy - MMOABC

**MMOABC Website Privacy Policy Statement**

**This document was last updated on March 1, 2010.**

**  
1\. Acknowledgement and Acceptance of Terms**

GameZoom Corporation., (“MMOABC”) is committed to protecting your Privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current Privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing [http://www.mmoabc.com](http://www.mmoabc.com/ "http://www.mmoabc.com"), you acknowledge and fully understand MMOABC’s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.

**  
2\. Participating Merchant Policies**

Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own Privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in MMOABC services are encouraged to participate in industry Privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer Privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the Privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the Privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

**  
3\. Information We Collect and How We Use It**

MMOABC collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies.

**  
Web Server Logs**

When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:  

  * Your Internet protocol address.
  * The kind of browser or computer you use.
  * Number of links you click within the site.
  * State or country from which you accessed the site.
  * Date and time of your visit.
  * Name of your Internet service provider.
  * Web page you linked to our site from.
  * Pages you viewed on the site.  

**Use of Cookies**

MMOABC may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality.

MMOABC reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into [http://www.mmoabc.com](http://www.mmoabc.com/) a site that relies on third-party cookies).

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

**Personal Information Users**

Visitors to our website can register to purchase services. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number or facsimile number, account number and other relevant information. If you are purchasing a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.

We may disclose at our discretion personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:  

  * To fulfill your service requests for services.
  * To sell and advertise related services to you in the form of emails, mailings and verbal communication.
  * To enter you into game contests, sweepstakes, game beta testing, promotions and events.
  * To protect ourselves from liability.
  * To respond to legal process or comply with law.
  * In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

**  
4\. Use of Web Beacons or GIF files**

http://www.mmoabc.com web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons – sometimes also called single-pixel gifs – that allow MMOABC to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. MMOABC may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. MMOABC prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.

**  
5\. Accessing Web Account Information**

We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by contacting us by sending an email to our support attendant contact@mmoabc.com.

**  
6\. No Information About Children**

Our Service is not intended to be used by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly, directly or passively, collect information from children under the age of 13. If we create offers and products that make it appropriate to collect information from children under the age of 13, we will notify you of the change in this Policy.

**  
7\. Network and Information Security**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your personal information. While we have taken efforts to guard your personal information, we cannot guarantee that your information may be not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others. Your account information and access to our Service is accessible only through the use of an individual user ID and password. To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of our Site and Service by any person using your account user ID and password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your account user ID and password have been misused.

**  
8\. Access and Control of Personal Information**

If you are a registered user of our Service, you may view, correct, and delete your personal information, and opt in to (or out of) receiving communications or solicitations, simply by logging into the Service and editing your profile. In addition, you may delete comments or images you have posted as part of your use of the Service. Generally, you should be careful when making any personal information available to the public. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to our Service and Site, such as customer service responses and other administrative messages.

**  
9\. California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not provide your personal information to any third party for their direct marketing purposes without your consent.

**  
10\. International Users**

By using our Site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of MMOABC, we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. Please note that your personal information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may be less stringent than the laws of your country. If you object to your personal information being transferred or used as described in this Policy, please do not register for the Service.

**  
11\. Changes to this Statement**

MMOABC has the discretion to occasionally update this Privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy statement and any updates.

**  
12\. Contacting Us**

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us. Email us at contact@mmoabc.com.
